<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Places</title>
    <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Places</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 15:47:54 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 03 Oct 2021 14:30:49 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi, my name is Shawn, and this is a simple travel blog site. It&amp;rsquo;s meant to capture observations of the places that my wife Shondy and I visited as we traveled by car around the United States during the pandemic years of 2020 and 2021. However, it also includes some trails and backcountry areas I hiked as side-trips where we had extended stays.
This blog site is achieved courtesy of several neat, modern technologies that make running your own static website easy.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Eugene, Oregon</title>
      <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/eugene-or/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Jun 2021 22:04:26 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/eugene-or/</guid>
      <description>For all our shared photos while in Oregon, see our Photo Gallery at /gallery/or Placeholder for Eugene, Oregon</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Boise, Idaho</title>
      <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/boise-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 01 May 2021 16:41:11 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/boise-id/</guid>
      <description>For all our shared photos while in Idaho, see our Photo Gallery at /gallery/id Try, Try Again When we first visited here last fall (see previous post here ), we didn&amp;rsquo;t feel like we got a good-enough look around the area. Winter was setting in alongside COVID, and it made getting out a bit tough.
So we opted for a second visit. This time, we secured an AirBnB apartment in the highly desirable and eclectic north-end Boise neighborhood.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Arvada, Colorado</title>
      <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/arvada-co/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 03 Apr 2021 16:41:03 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/arvada-co/</guid>
      <description>For all our shared photos while in Colorado, see our Photo Gallery at /gallery/co &amp;ldquo;Oh Lord, When will Winter be Over?&amp;rdquo; We arrived in Arvada, Colorado, a suburb of Denver, the second week of March 2021 for a month-long stay. I was excited. We were visiting family in the area, and I was told the weather was looking nice. Spring was coming. Hooray! Since November, we&amp;rsquo;d been bearing through cold and snow and ice traveling in Oregon, Idaho, Utah, Arizona (yes, Arizona had snow, see my blog post here ), Texas, and Arkansas.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bentonville, Arkansas</title>
      <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/bentonville-ar/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Mar 2021 08:22:41 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/bentonville-ar/</guid>
      <description>For all our shared photos while in Arkansas, see our Photo Gallery at /gallery/ar Northwest Arkansas &amp;ndash; There&amp;rsquo;s a Whole Different Thing Going On Whatever picture you have in your head about Arkansas&amp;ndash; throw it out. Especially if your first foray into the state is anywhere along the Interstate 49 corridor that comprises Northwest Arkansas&amp;ndash; a.k.a. NWA for short.
If you are familiar with retail, you probably know that Bentonville is the headquarters and home office of Walmart, the Fortune 1 company (note: Fortune 1 &amp;ndash; not Fortune 100) that employs a 2.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Conway, Arkansas</title>
      <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/conway-ar/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 Feb 2021 16:40:45 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/conway-ar/</guid>
      <description>For all our shared photos while in Arkansas, see our Photo Gallery at /gallery/ar Friendly People, Fabulous Names OK, so right off the top, let me jump into a couple observations about Arkansas:
 Friendly People. Call it Southern courtesy, or simply good manners&amp;ndash; whatever you want&amp;ndash; but compared to Western states, it was very noticeable how friendly people are in Arkansas. And it goes beyond the &amp;ldquo;yes ma&amp;rsquo;am&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;yes sir&amp;rdquo; etiquette.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Cochise County, Arizona</title>
      <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/cochiseco-az/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 31 Jan 2021 22:28:38 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/cochiseco-az/</guid>
      <description>For all our shared photos while in Arizona, see our Photo Gallery at /gallery/az Southern Arizona - Desert for Non-Desert People I highly recommend visiting Arizona. It&amp;rsquo;s uniquely beautiful. You can&amp;rsquo;t stand next to a Saguaro or Cholla cactus and not be impressed with how life persists in an extemely hot, dry environment. Desert vistas with their orange, gold, and yellow hues coloring the dawn (or dusk) are brilliant. You don&amp;rsquo;t get that from other landscapes.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Zion National Park, Utah</title>
      <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/zion-ut/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 31 Dec 2020 22:01:20 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/zion-ut/</guid>
      <description>For all our shared photos while in Utah, see our Photo Gallery at /gallery/ut Only One Thing to Say: GO! I could use all sorts of superlatives, and heap all sorts of praise, on how great Zion National Park is. And it would all be true.
But I&amp;rsquo;d be articulating poorly what so many other writers, artists, outdoor enthusiasts, etc. have, in the past, stated better. Instead, I&amp;rsquo;ll let the photos speak for themselves.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Vineyard, Utah</title>
      <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/vineyard-ut/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 29 Dec 2020 17:04:12 -3100</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/vineyard-ut/</guid>
      <description>For all our shared photos while in Utah, see our Photo Gallery at /gallery/ut The Newly Minted City We arrived in Vineyard, Utah at the start of December 2020. We came here to visit family living in the Salt Lake City area. Too, a few friends we know spoke highly of SLC, and how it&amp;rsquo;s becoming a popular destination for people looking for tech jobs. So we figured a two-week stay outta cover our family visit&amp;ndash; and our curiosity to see why it&amp;rsquo;s so attractive.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Meridian, Idaho</title>
      <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/meridian-id/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 12 Dec 2020 21:32:12 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/meridian-id/</guid>
      <description>For all our shared photos while in Idaho, see our Photo Gallery at /gallery/id Wait.. this is Idaho?!? Until we crossed the Snake River driving from Oregon along Interstate 84, I had never been to Idaho. It was the second week of November, 2020, and the weather was borderline snow with ice laden clouds overhead, ready to burst.
That snow part&amp;ndash; yep, I expected that. Along with snow, the picture I had in my head of Idaho was a place of tall mountains, pine forests, rivers running free, clean air, no crowds, bears walking across the road from time-to-time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Bend, Oregon</title>
      <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/bend-or/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 20 Nov 2020 09:39:55 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/bend-or/</guid>
      <description>For all our shared photos while in Oregon, see our Photo Gallery at /gallery/or If I had come here long before, I would have moved here&amp;hellip; Our stay in Bend was brief&amp;ndash; less than a week. Which is unfortunate. I should have stayed a month.
Or maybe the rest of my life.
Let me explain. I&amp;rsquo;ve spent the majority of my life living in Santa Cruz, California, which IMHO is unmatched by most locale&amp;rsquo;s on this planet.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Placerville, California</title>
      <link>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/placerville-ca/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 03 Nov 2020 16:39:47 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sown87.github.io/our-journey/posts/placerville-ca/</guid>
      <description>For all our shared photos while in the Placerville area, see our Photo Gallery at /gallery/ca Placerville: not just a Place to Pass Through Our stay in Placerville wasn&amp;rsquo;t unfamiliar. We&amp;rsquo;ve been through it several times on the way to South Lake Tahoe, perhaps taking time to stop at one of the busiest In-N-Out restaurants in the entire chain. Most Sierra Nevada foothill towns like Placerville take on a &amp;ldquo;pass-through&amp;rdquo; identity for people heading to higher-elevation recreation sites for skiing, hiking, backpacking, etc.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
